易考范文十五
What we can see are two shocking drawings.
In the first one,
black clouds of exhaust fume are emitted from a high chimney.
In the second, a signal tower stands instead of the ugly chimney,
sending out invisible harmful radiation.
The problem revealed in the drawings has, indeed,
aroused nationwide concern.
Nowadays, some local governments are in hot pursuit of economic development,
as a result of which people's income has increased.
At the same time, however,
their health is being threatened by the worsening environment,
which is the side effect of blind expansion in economy.
It has been generally accepted that
it is unwise to sacrifice people's welfare for short-term interest.
However, there is no doubt that we cannot put the cart before the horse
by halting economic progress solely for the sake of our health,
as development is definitely an irreversible trend.
As far as I am concerned, firstly,
it is imperative for governments at all levels
to put more stress on environmental protection
so as to ensure the harmonious coexistence of nature and economy.
Secondly,
in addition to the strict implementation of laws and regulations concerning environment,
the government's strengthened awareness of the public well-being
will contribute to the solution of this issue.